tripmegamart.com 2016-10-18

# Cheapest Flight Tickets, Hotels, Car Booking, Bus Tickets, Domestic & International Holiday Packages - TripMegaMart.com

**Privacy Policy**

We have developed this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy and the protection of your information. As part of the operation of services, we collect and, in some instances, disclose information about you. This privacy policy has been developed to keep you informed of what personally identifiable information we may collect from you, what this information will be used for, with whom such information will be shared, and the security procedures we have implemented to protect your privacy.   
Information collected by us

General Browsing

In general, this website may be visited and browsed by you without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information. However, as you browse through this website, the site collects the log file, IP address of your computer, and other standard tracking data which we use to evaluate site traffic and usage patterns. Such information is aggregated with tracking data from all site visitors. We will use the information to personalize the site according to your preferences based on the aggregated information. We also use the aggregated information to evaluate products and services we may offer to you.

Collection of Personal Information

Some portions of this website may require you to give us personally identifiable information (personal information) such as your name, telephone number, fax number, postal and e-mail addresses; your credit card number, expiration date of your credit card and other details, with relation to your credit card. In order to make your travel and other arrangements, we may also require you to provide us with information about your travel requirements, ticketing options and other preferences.

You may opt not to provide us with your personal information; however, unless you provide us such personal information, you may not be able to access and utilize the products and services offered by us. Requirement of your personal information is a must for you to register as our member, purchase products and services from this website, participate in a survey or contest, raise a query or for the purpose of completing any transaction on this website.

Cookies and Web Beacons

To enhance your experience with this website, many of our web pages use "cookies." Cookies are text files we place in your computer s browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not provide us with any of your personal information unless you choose to provide this information to us as aforesaid. However, once you choose to furnish the site with your personal information, your information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie. We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on this website. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages for e.g., to recognize you by name when you return to our site), save your password in password-protected areas, and enable you to use shopping carts on our sites. We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs, or services.

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies. However, you can always choose not to accept a cookie by changing your computer preferences to refuse cookies or to prompt you to accept each cookie. Please note that in the event that you do refuse to accept cookies, you may not be able to access and utilise many of the products and services offered by us.

We may also use "Web beacons" or clear.gifs on this website. "Web beacons" or clear.gifs are small pieces of codes placed on a web page to monitor the behaviour and collect data about the visitors viewing a web page. For e.g., web beacons can be used to count the users who visit a web page or to deliver a cookie to the browser of a visitor viewing that page.

Collection of information by third party sites

Some of our sites contain links to other sites (third party sites) whose information practices may be different than ours. These third party sites may use cookies, web beacons, clear .gifs or similar technologies to help present such advertisements, and to help measure and research the advertisements effectiveness. The use of these technologies by these third party sites is subject to their own privacy policies and is not covered by our privacy policy. Visitors should consult the other sites privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties sites.

Sponsored and co-branded content

This website may offer content (e.g., contests, sweepstakes, or promotions), that is sponsored by or co-branded with identified third parties. By virtue of these relationships, the third parties may obtain personal information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the site activity. We have no control over these third parties use of this information.

Usage of information provided to us

We use the personal information provided by you to effectively complete your order towards the purchase of our products and services, fulfil any customer service requests, provide promotional information, notify you about special offers and products or services that may be of interest to you and to otherwise customise your experience with this website. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete your order and fulfil your travel arrangements and with the entities mentioned in this Privacy Policy.

Sharing and /of information

Suppliers such as hotels, airlines, car rental companies, or activity providers, who fulfil and complete your travel reservations. All products and services provided by a third-party supplier are described as such on this website. We share personal information with such suppliers only to the extent necessary. However, we cannot place limitations on our suppliers use or disclosure of your personal information. Therefore, we encourage you to review the privacy policies of any travel supplier whose products you purchase through this website.

Business partners with whom we may jointly offer products or services. All products and services provided jointly with such business partners are easily identifiable by virtue of their names/ trademarks being associated with such products or services. If you choose to access these optional services, we may have to share your personal information, with those business partners. Please note that we do not control the privacy practices of these business partners and recommend you evaluate their practices before deciding to provide your personal information.

To the extent that our group entities have access to your personal information, they will follow practices that are at least as restrictive as the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

We may disclose the personal information we collect when we have reason to believe that it is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against persons or entities who may be causing or are likely to cause injury to you, to us, or to others. We may also disclose your personal information when we believe the law requires it.

We also may share aggregate or anonymous information with third parties, including advertisers and investors. For e.g., we may tell our advertisers the most preferred airline, destination, etc. This information does not contain any personal information and is used to develop content and services we hope you will find of interest.

Security

The security and confidentiality of your personal information is of utmost concern to us. However, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be completely secure. As a result, while we will use our best reasonable efforts to protect your information, though we cannot warrant or guarantee the security of any information you may transmit to us. In order to protect the information stored in our systems, we have implemented security measures, including data encryption technology and firewalls.

Minors

Minors are not eligible to register for, or use, or purchase the products and services available on this website. We do not knowingly collect or solicit any personal information from any minor.

Contact Us

If you have questions, comments or concerns about this Privacy Policy please send us an email:  [support@tripmegamart.com](mailto:support@tripmegamart.com)

Consent

By using this website, you consent to the collection, use, and storage of your information by us in the manner described in this Privacy Policy and elsewhere on this website.

Amendment

We reserve the right to change, modify or amend this policy at any time. Please check our Privacy Policy periodically for changes. Use of this website after modification implies that you consent to this Privacy Policy as modified.
